https://amberwavespygmygoats.com/page.php?page=privacy

Advanced
Home »
Goats as Pets
Great Pyrenees Is It Right For You?
Scrapies - USDA
Seasonal Goat Care (Winter, Summer, Fall, Spring)
website (the “Website”) collects certain personally
identifiable information, which may be used to provide you with
customized services, content, networking opportunities, industry
information and/or advertisements. Personally identifiable information
is collected when you register to receive certain Website products
and/or services. The Website may also request personally identifiable
information when the user elects to participate in other Website
affiliated or sponsored programs, including, but not limited to,
sweepstakes, contests, and/or other such promotions.
Upon the consent
of the user, the Website may share the collected personally
identifiable information with a sponsor or other third party that may
be interested in serving you. The Website will request and verify your
consent before any personally identifiable information is provided to
sponsors or third parties. You may also inform Website, at any time,
not to share your personally identifiable information with third
parties by sending an e-mail message to info@amberwaves.com requesting
that your personally identifiable information not be released to third
parties.
The Website may
use your personally identifiable information to provide you with any
services to which you subscribe, and any service-related activities,
such as collecting subscription fees for such services, and notifying
you or contacting you with regard to any problem with, or the
expiration of, such services. For this reason, the Website may find it
necessary to disclose your personally identifiable information to one
or more Website agents and/or contractors and their subcontractors, but
such agents, contractors, and subcontractors must agree to use any
personally identifiable information obtained from Website for only such
purposes.
Personally
identifiable information also may be disclosed to the proper
authorities in special situations where the Website has reason to
believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal
action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally
or unintentionally) with the Website’s rights, property,
users, or anyone else who may be harmed by such activities. The Website
may reveal personally identifiable information when we have been
required to do so by law enforcement authorities, or have established a
good faith belief that the law requires that the Website do so.
The Website
reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time by posting
revisions on the Website. This privacy policy is not intended to, and
does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf
of any party.
Merck Animal Health
Animal Health Center of Madison: Madison, MS Veterinarian Clinic
Federal and State Animal Health
Popular Links
American Boer Goat Association | ABGA.org
Hamby Dairy Supply
Pygora Goats and More Available at Crown Meadow in Scio, Oregon
News for Livestock+dogs
Dog Owner's Guide: Livestock guard dogs
Top Rated Videos
Castrating 200+ Pound Calf - Humane Castration of Cow With Elastrator Tool & Rubber Bands Tutorial
Why Disbud Your Goats?
How To Potty Train In Less Than Day
Baby Goat Compilation!
For a goat Castration......
Amber Waves Pygmy Goats
Culture Magazine : The word on Cheese Culture Magazine : The word on Cheese Boston, MA About Blog Culture is the ultimate publication for those who love cheese. Our bi-monthly magazine is devoted to delivering the most innovative, eye-opening stories abou
Hoegger Supply Company Goat Health Blog
Popular Blogs
Culture Magazine : The word on Cheese Culture Magazine : The word on Cheese Boston, MA About Blog Culture is the ultimate publication for those who love cheese. Our bi-monthly magazine is devoted to delivering the most innovative, eye-opening stories abou
Meat Goat Blog
Amber Waves Pygmy Goats
Hoegger Supply Company Goat Health Blog
Hoegger Cheese Making Blog
Top Rated News
New Arrival - African Pygmy Doe Kid For Sale
Extension Sheboygan County
Annual flu vaccines recommended for social dogs
Los Angeles County Urban Agriculture Regulations
Orange County decides: goats are a no go in residential neighborhoods
Popular News
What Goats Can't Eat Around Your Homestead Including Table Scraps!
Feeding on extra cold days... 'I'm starving' (lol)
Forgot cash app pin
Quail?
Los Angeles County Urban Agriculture Regulations
Top Rated Articles
Abortion
Angora Goats - A Small-Scale Agriculture Alternative
Causes of Infectious Abortions in Goats
Caseous Lymphadenitis (CL) and Pinkeye
Sore Mouth In Goats
Popular Articles
17 Facts You Didn't Know About Goats - From Screaming to Swimming
Just How "Mini" is a Pygmy Goat?
Chicken Vs. Goat Manure: Which Is Best?
What Is the Difference Between an African Pygmy Goat and a Nigerian Dwarf Goat?
Pennsylvania 4-H
Home
Contact
Search
Privacy Statement
Website Disclaimers
Copyright Notice
Site Map
Important! Please Read This Notice!
It is your responsibility to obtain veterinary services and advice before using any of the information provided in these articles, videos or links.
Debbie and/or Jim Hosley are not a veterinarian. Neither Amberwavespygmygoats.com nor any of the contributors to this website will be held responsible for the use of any information contained herein.
